Guide to the Afro-American Cultural Center at Yale Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Afro-American Cultural Center at Yale records
1960-2006
RU 957
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
27.27
57 boxes
43212.8
The records consist of correspondence, reports, minutes and agendas, programs, newsletters, news clippings, photographs and digital images, oral histories, exhibit records, and posters documenting the activities and programs of the Afro-American Cultural Center and African-Americans at Yale.
Yale University. Afro-American Cultural Center
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 37 (YRG 37), Records of associations, institutes, centers, and organizations affiliated with Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to this collection requires permission of the Director of the Afro-American Cultural Center. Additional restrictions may apply in certain accessions. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Biographical / Historical
The Afro-American Cultural Center at Yale (originally called Afro-America Cultural Center) was established in 1968 in response to concerns raised by the Black Student Alliance at Yale [BSAY).
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, reports, minutes and agendas, programs, newsletters, news clippings, photographs and digital images, oral histories, exhibit records, and posters documenting the activities and programs of the Afro-American Cultural Center and African-Americans at Yale.
African American college students; African Americans; Student affairs services; Photographs; Black Student Alliance at Yale; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Afro-American Cultural Center
- African American Cultural Center records, Circa 1967-2001; Accession 2005-A-002
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 3,4,7,14 and 15 contain student information that are restricted until January 1, 2077. Restrictions are noted at the file level within the inventory.
  - Black Student Alliance (BSAY)
    - Early Leaders
      - Glenn de Chabert, 1970-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
      - Craig Foster (Box 1, Folder 3 - 4)
      - Don Ogilvie [empty] (Box 1, Folder 5 - 6)
      - Armstead L. Robinson, 1967, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7 - 8)
    - SPLIBS, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Varied: correspondence, reviews, founding, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Founding Days, correspondence, African American program, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Wisconsin conference, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Afro-American Studies-Black Studies report, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Founders, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - New Haven Public Schools, 1970, 1975, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - South and Southern Africa activism, 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Letter to board of directors leadership, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Founders, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Founders Steering committee minutes, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Founders, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Afro-America Inc., trustee minutes, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Founders, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1999 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Yale University Wide Tribunal, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Activism Against Racism at Yale, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - BSAY and Third World Coalition, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Study Group, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Points of Information and Clarification, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Open End Theater Co., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Minutes and notes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Membership, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Community Organizations and event flyers, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Yale Alumni Club of Queens, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Vienna Carroll Opening Address, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Steering committee regarding governance, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Revised BSAY Constitution, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Black Grad/Prof Students letter to President Brewster, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Minority Special Summer Programs re: Biology, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - J.D. Hackman: Minority Students Report, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Letter to Community Organizations re: Mandela, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Black Student Union [BSU], 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Puerto Rican Students, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Political Education Study Cell, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Officers of Minority Student Groups, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Newspaper articles, 1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Transcript of Ad-Hoc advisory committee, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Archivist [Job Description], 1978 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Discussion Group of Negro Affairs, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Afro-American Studies memo "Ten Years After", 1978 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Historical overviews, 1978, 1982-1983, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Reports of Police Harassment, 1977, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Constitution, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Minority Advisory Council [MAC], 1979 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - BSAY and Minority Student Groups, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Minority Admissions Advisory Committee [MAC], 1980 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Membership forms and roster, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Lists of Black Films, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - "Investments in South Africa," Stat Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Intercollegiate Activities, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Professor Charles T. Davis [Memorial], 1981 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Newsletters, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - "Logbook" BSAY Moderators and Members, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Kwame Toure [Stokely Carmichael], 1982 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Haitian Refugees, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Gay and lesbian awareness, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Black Ivy Conference, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Anti-Nestle Campaign, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Afro-American Studies chairs/directors list, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1985, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Black Solidarity Day, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Election Issues, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - PROP Review Committee, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Presidential Candidates: Reagan, Jackson, Mondale, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Political Education Nigeria, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Newsletters Received, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Local 34 Strike, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Black Solidarity Day Flyer, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Law Students, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Black History Month, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Agenda/Minutes, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Membership Lists, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Program Corp of America [Booklet], 1985 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Gwendolyn Brooks [MLK], 1985 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Manning Marable, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Community Outreach List, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Black Students at Yale College, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Black Solidarity Day, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Black Professional Students, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - SECHABA [South Africa's ANC Publication], 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - BSAY Posts Candidate Platforms [Fall], 1986 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - BSAY Agendas/Minutes [Fall], 1986 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Updates: Various Committees, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Political Education Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Correspondence and Agendas, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - AACC Membership and Committee Lists, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Membership and Attendance, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Gen. Goals, Evaluations, Achievements, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Fiscal overview, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Community outreach committee, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - AACC annual reports, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Newspaper articles, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Affirmative Action committee, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Newspaper articles, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - 20th Anniversary press release, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Steering committee minutes, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Evaluation minutes, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Calendar events, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Agendas and minutes, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Journals and newsletters, 1987-1989, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - 25th anniversary flyer and ribbon, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Resident group officers list, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Resident group duties and responsibilities, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - AACC membership forms
      - 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 116)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 117)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 118)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 119 - 120)
      - 1990 (Box 2, Folder 121 - 122)
    - Staff agendas/minutes, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - National African American student leadership summit, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - "The Juice Problem" [play] incomplete manuscript, Undated (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Steering committee, Undated (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Political education, Undated (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Greg Hampton poetry, Undated (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Evaluation committee list: problems/solutions, Undated (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - The Committee, Undated (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Black at Yale, Undated (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Files-budget (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - All African Peoples revolutionary party, Undated (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Directors
    - Correspondence [Moore], 1971 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Correspondence [Roland Powell], 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Correspondence [Khalid Eric Lum], 1974 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Annual Report [Lum], 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 138 - 139)
    - Recommendations [Lum], 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Correspondence [Lum], 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 141 - 143)
    - Searches, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Appointment [Patricia Romney], 1979 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Recommendations [Romney], 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 148 - 149)
    - Guidelines/Responses/By-Laws, 1981-1988 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Annual Report [Caroline B. Jackson], 1981 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Monthly Reports to Board [Jackson], 1982-1989 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Recommendations and References [Jackson], 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Recommendations [Jackson], 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Faculty John Blassingame Correspondence [seeboxes 14-15], 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Recommendations [Jackson] [Restricted] (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - M. Anisman Recommendation [Jackson], 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Recommendations [Jackson], 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - 3rd World Undergrad. Weekend [Jackson], 1979-1984 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Minority Affairs Procedures [Jackson], 1980-1988 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Correspondence [Jackson], 1981-1987 (Box 3, Folder 161 - 162)
    - House Updates [Jackson], 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Correspondence [Jackson] [Restricted]
      - 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 164)
      - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 165)
      - 1986 (Box 3, Folder 166)
      - 1987 (Box 3, Folder 167)
      - 1988 (Box 3, Folder 168)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 169)
      - 1989 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Annual Report [Melvin Wade], 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - Correspondence [Wade], 1990 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Monthly Report to Board [Wade], 1991 (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Correspondence [Wade], 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Correspondence [Kimberly Goff-Crews], 1992-1996 (Box 3, Folder 175 - 176)
    - Resume [Goff-Crews], 1994 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Student Recommendation Letters, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - Sylvia Ardyn Boon [Memorial], 1993, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Board of Directors [Restricted]
    - Correspondence, 1972-1979 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Agendas and Minutes, 1973-1979 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Grants/Proposals, 1974-1978 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - Project Proposal for AACC Development, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Agendas, Minutes, Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Retreat, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Diagnostic and Assessment Reports, 1980-1983, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - AACC Survey/Summary, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - AACC Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Agendas and Minutes, 1980-1989 (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1989 (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Resumes, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Retreat, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Agendas and Minutes, 1990-1996 (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Minutes and Correspondence, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - Jr. Board Agendas and Minutes, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Listing, 1977-1996 (Box 4, Folder 198 - 200)
    - Minority Advisory Council [MAC]
      - Listing, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 201)
      - History and Purpose, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 202)
      - Reports, 1982-1988 (Box 4, Folder 203)
      - Agenda and Minutes, 1981-1989 (Box 4, Folder 204)
      - Correspondence, 1982-1989 (Box 4, Folder 205)
      - Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 206)
      - Agenda and Minutes, 1991-1999 (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - Pre-Registration Orientation Program [PROP]
      - Preparations, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 208)
      - Aide Applicants, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 209)
      - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 210)
      - Lists, Schedules, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 211)
      - Writing Tutors, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 212)
  - Administration and Finance
    - Facility Rental Guidelines/Contracts, 1971-1979 (Box 4, Folder 213)
    - Budget Correspondence/Reports, 1971, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 214)
    - Advertising Contracts, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 215)
    - Renaissance 2, Copyright Certificates and Correspondence, 1972, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 216)
    - Renaissance 2, Correspondence, Annual Report, 1972-1976 (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - Personnel Policies/Procedures/Correspondence, 1972-1979 (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - Amistad Film Project: John Moore, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 219)
    - Staff, 1974-1979 (Box 4, Folder 220)
    - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 221)
    - AACC Long Range Plan, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 222)
    - Security/Key, 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - Staff Memo, 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 224)
    - Library Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 225)
    - Consulting Agreements, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - Student Time Sheets, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - Student Time Sheets, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - Library Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - Grant Applications, 1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - Staff Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - Security/Keys, 1980-1987 (Box 4, Folder 232)
    - Staff Guidelines/Mission Statement, 1980-1988 (Box 4, Folder 233)
    - Staff Agendas, 1980-1988 (Box 4, Folder 234)
    - Requisitions Undergrad Student Employees, 1980-1988 (Box 4, Folder 235)
    - Facility Requests/Contracts, 1980-1988 (Box 4, Folder 236)
    - Staff Memo, 1980-1989 (Box 4, Folder 237)
    - Staff Listing, 1980-1989 (Box 4, Folder 238)
    - Service Invoices, 1980-1989 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Admin Assistant Applications, 1980-1989 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Budget Financial Reports, 1980-1990 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Theater Grant Application [Oyamo Playwright], 1981 (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - AACC Diagnosis by School of Management, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Artists-in-Residence Proposal, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Staff Evaluations, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - Publication Correspondence with Patrons, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Black Big Brothers and Sisters, 1981-1982, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - Greetings Cards, Letters, 1981, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - Weekly Staff Reports, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - AACC By-Laws, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Student Staff Applications, 1982-1988 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - Black Church at Yale -Program, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - Student Staff Applications, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - Afro-American Studies Faculty List, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - Monthly Staff Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - Gift Accounts/Gift Memos, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Staff Weekly Hours and Schedules, 1985-1990 (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - Black Arts and Craft Fair, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - Mumbo Jumbo Films, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 261)
    - Management and Fiscal Development Plan, 1987-1990 (Box 5, Folder 263)
    - Minority Summer Research Exchange Program, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 264)
    - AACC Award Surveys, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 265)
    - AACC/Yale Black Artists of Fame, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 266)
    - Student Applications, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - Mural Project, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 268)
    - Staff Evaluations, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 270)
    - Office Procedures/Policies/Guidelines, 1989-1995 (Box 5, Folder 272)
    - Arts Council Membership, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 273)
    - Facility Requests, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 274)
    - Building History [211 Park St], AACC House Proposal, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 275)
    - Graduate Assistant, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 276)
    - Graduate/Undergrad Class of 1990, Honors, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 277)
    - Staff Applications/Officers, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 278)
    - Staff Evaluation/Job Descriptions, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 279)
    - Staff Memos, 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 281)
    - Security, 1990-1995 (Box 5, Folder 282)
    - Staff Agendas, 1990-19999 (Box 5, Folder 283)
    - Black Employees at Yale, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 284)
    - Senior Awards Program/Graduating Class, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 285)
    - Dennis Greene -Resume/Application, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 287)
    - Greetings Cards/Letters, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 288)
    - Budget Guidelines/Memos/Reports, 1990-1996 (Box 5, Folder 289)
    - Annual Budget Reports, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 290)
    - Academic Mentoring Program in Sciences [AMPS], 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 291)
    - The Tuesday Connection and Minority Staff Statistics Report, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 292)
    - Student Applications, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 293)
    - T-Shirts Design and Invoice, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 294)
    - Staff Schedules, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 295)
  - Resident Groups
    - Black Pre-Law Society, 1974-1990 (Box 5, Folder 296)
    - Black Law Students, 1975-1976, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 297)
    - Varied Resident Groups Correspondence, 1975-1984 (Box 5, Folder 298)
    - Yale Gospel Choir, 1975-1999 (Box 6, Folder 299)
    - Black Pre-Professional Council, 1977-1992 (Box 6, Folder 300)
    - Resident Group Organizations, 1977-1999 (Box 6, Folder 301)
    - Nzinga Dancers, 1978, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 302)
    - Black Women Literary Salon, 1979, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 303)
    - Delta Sigma Theta, Inc., 1979, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 304)
    - Resident Group Organizations and Guidelines, 1980-1986 (Box 6, Folder 305)
    - Resident Organizations and Guidelines, 1980-1986 (Box 6, Folder 306)
    - African American Friendship Society, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 307)
    - Black Undergraduate Women's Group, 1982-1986 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha, 1982-1992 (Box 6, Folder 309)
    - Minority BSN Association at Yale, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 310)
    - Resident Group Meetings [Agendas/Minutes], 1982-1998 (Box 6, Folder 311)
    - Black Church at Yale, 1982-1999 (Box 6, Folder 312)
    - Black Professionals Colloquium, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 313)
    - HEKAH (Box 6, Folder 314)
      - Portfolio, 1971-1984 (Box 6, Folder 315)
      - Production Flyers, 1983-1995 (Box 6, Folder 316)
      - Correspondence, 1984-1995 (Box 6, Folder 317)
      - Flyers and Magazines, 1985-1995 (Box 6, Folder 318)
      - Portfolio, 1988-1993 (Box 6, Folder 319)
      - Barbara O. [Actress], 1992 (Box 6, Folder 320)
      - Proposals, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 321)
      - Community Service Organizations, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 322)
      - Social Functions Policies, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 323)
      - Members and Alumni, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 325)
    - Black Tie Society, 1983-1987 (Box 6, Folder 326)
    - Alpha Kappa Alpha [AKA], 1984-1993 (Box 6, Folder 327)
    - Heritage Theater Ensemble, Constitution, 1981, 1984-1994 (Box 6, Folder 328)
    - Resident Organizations Guidelines and Policies, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 329)
    - Varied Resident Groups Correspondence, 1985-1998 (Box 6, Folder 330)
    - Action for Racial Equality, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 331)
    - Caribbean Club, 1986-1999 (Box 6, Folder 332)
    - Kappa Alpha Psi, 1987-1998 (Box 6, Folder 333)
    - Campus Against Racial Violence [C.A.R.V.], 1988 (Box 6, Folder 334)
    - African American Pre-Medical Association, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 335)
    - SHADES, 1989-1997 (Box 6, Folder 336)
    - Black Business Network [BSN], 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 337)
    - Agape Bible and Prayer Fellowship, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 338)
    - The Forum, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 339)
    - Students of Color for Reproductive Health, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 340)
    - Omega Psi Phi, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 341)
    - In the Eyes of God, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 342)
    - Collective and Self-Empowerment [C.A.S.E.], 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 343)
    - Resident Group Guidelines, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 344)
    - Zeta Phi Beta, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 345)
    - Black Pride Union, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 346)
    - Yale African Student Association, 1995-1999 (Box 6, Folder 347)
    - PAALS, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 348)
    - National Council of Negro Women, Inc. [Yale Chapter], 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 349)
    - National Coalition of 100 Black Women, Inc., 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 350)
    - BLAZE, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 351)
    - Yale Black Political Forum, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 352)
    - Black Graduate Network [BGN] Correspond., Posters, Flyers, 1981-1989 (Box 7, Folder 353)
    - BGN Membership Forms, 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 354)
    - BGN Receipts, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 355)
    - National Society of Black Engineers, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 356)
    - Steppin19 Out, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 357)
    - King's Men Bible Study, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 358)
    - Alliance for Cultural Evolution, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 359)
    - NAACP [Yale Chapter]
      - Guidelines/Procedures, 1988-1998 (Box 7, Folder 360)
      - Newsletters, Articles, Flyers, 1992-1993, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 361)
      - Meeting Agenda, 1993, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 362)
      - Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 363)
      - Membership, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 364)
    - Klub Kreyol: Haitian Student Alliance at Yale, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 365)
  - House Programs and Events
    - Isaac Hayes [Singer], 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 366)
    - Jodi Braxton [Writer], 1971-1976 (Box 7, Folder 367)
    - Theater House Programs, 1971-1994 (Box 7, Folder 368)
    - Aturo Lindsay [Artist], 1971-1980 (Box 7, Folder 369)
    - Self-Taught Exhibition, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 370)
    - Ntozake Shange [Playwright], 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 371)
    - Poets and Writers Magazines, 1974, 1976, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 372)
    - House Program Activities [Correspondence], 1973-1981 (Box 7, Folder 373)
    - Poets and Writers Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box 7, Folder 374)
    - House Program Flyers [Six Folders], 1974-1999 (Box 7, Folder 375)
    - Poets and Writers Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box 7, Folder 376)
    - Event Programs, 1974-1981 (Box 7, Folder 377)
    - Thurmond White Proposal "Allensworth", 1975 (Box 7, Folder 378)